psiexams.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | PSI Services LLC

PSI Services LLC (“PSI”) recognizes that its customers, exam candidates, and PSI website (the “Site”) users value their privacy. PSI strives to protect personal information collected through its business or generated through the Site, and maintained in PSI’s business files, records, databases, or the Site (the “Files”).

**Information Collected, Generated and Maintained**

_Licensure Testing Candidates:_

Whether a candidate registers and completes an exam in person, or online using the ATLAS® platform, each candidate may be required to furnish some or all of the following personal information: first and last name, address, phone numbers, date of birth, email address, state identification number, social security number and credit card information, and at some testing locations digital photographs, fingerprints and/or signatures (collectively the “Personal Information”). All Personal Information is maintained in PSI’s Files. Once a candidate has completed an exam, testing content and results (collectively, the “Exam Information”) will be maintained in PSI’s Files.

_License Processing:_

Information related to any licensed candidates, such as license application information, license activity, license history, information relating to continuing education credits, public complaints, board actions taken against the licensee, or any public actions taken against licensee by regulatory boards or agencies (“Licensee Updates”) will be collected and maintained in PSI’s Files.

_Corporate Talent Assessment:_

Many of PSI’s clients are corporations (“Corporate Clients”) that use PSI’s system to deliver exams to their job candidates. As such, PSI collects and maintains the Personal Information and Exam Information of such job candidates, as well as job applicant demographics (collectively the “Job Demographics”) in PSI’s Files.

**_Parties To Whom Information May Be Disclosed & How Information Is Used_**

_Corporate Clients:_

With respect to our Corporate Clients only, Personal Information, Exam Information and Job Demographics are disclosed to such Corporate Clients who have used PSI’s system to deliver exams to their job candidates. Personal Information and Exam Information are never disclosed to individual candidates or unauthorized third parties, unless otherwise required by law.

_Third Parties:_

With respect to licensure testing candidates, Licensee Updates may be disclosed to licensing agencies, regulatory boards, state governments or professional associations for their files and records. Personal Information may only be disclosed to third parties or entities authorized by PSI. However, in certain States, the Personal Information, Exam Information, and Licensee Updates are considered information to be in the public domain and thus, third parties may access such information for a cost. In addition, PSI may, disclose Personal Information, Exam Information and Licensee Updates, under special circumstances when PSI has reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against one who may be causing injury to, or interfering with, PSI’s rights or property, other Site users, others that could be harmed by such activities, or as otherwise required by law.

_Data, Studies and Research:_

PSI uses the Exam Information and Job Demographics on an aggregate anonymous basis to support validation study and to develop normative data sets for use in PSI’s businesses for research or other scientific study. PSI does not use any Personal Information for such studies or research.

_Marketing_

PSI and its third party affiliates may communicate with registered users and customers through email and other methods from time to time. PSI and its third party affiliates will use their best efforts to only communicate with persons who “opt in” to such communications or with persons whose information is already deemed public information by their licensing authorities, and will cease communicating with any customers who “opt out” of such communications.

**_Confidentiality and Security_**

PSI is committed to protecting the Personal Information, Exam Information, Licensee Updates, and Job Demographics, and PSI has put in place various electronic safeguards and managerial processes to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data integrity, and ensure the appropriate use of such information. PSI maintains Personal Information, Exam Information and Licensee Updates on secured computers and all customers, exam candidates, and employer accounts are password protected. Of course, no such security and safeguards are 100% effective, but PSI will use its best efforts to employ state of the art security measures to protect such information. No personally identifiable information is knowingly disclosed to third parties except as described herein. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Thus, PSI cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information Site users transmit to the Site.

**_Additional Information_**

_Cookies_

To enhance the users experience with the Site, PSI may place a small text file called a “cookie” on a users computer hard-drive to store such users preferences. Users can examine and delete the cookie files on their computer at any time. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will explain how to prevent a browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify a user when it receives a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

_Links_

This Site may use content or provide links to third-party web sites that are not owned by PSI. PSI has no control over third parties and assumes no responsibility in connection with any users’ use of third party content or web sites. We recommend that users check the terms of use and privacy policy of any web site before users provide any personally identifiable information.

_IP Addresses_

An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to a computer whenever it is being used to surf the Web. Web servers automatically identify computers by their IP address. PSI may collect IP addresses for the purpose of system administration, to prepare aggregate information, and to monitor the use of this Site.

_Children_

This Site is not designed to attract anyone under the age of 13 and children under the age of 13 are not permitted to access or use the Site.

**_Privacy Policy Updates and Acceptance_**

PSI may update its Privacy Policy from time to time as conditions dictate. Customers, exam candidates, clients, and Site users are responsible for periodically checking for any updates. By using this Site, users signify their assent to this Policy as it is in effect at the time of such use. A users’ continued use of this Site following the posting of any changes to this Policy will mean that such user has accepted and agrees to be bound by those changes.

**_Questions or Problems_**

Should any customers, exam candidates, clients, or Site users have any questions or experience a personal information privacy problem, please contact PSI via phone or email [privacy@psionline.com](mailto:privacy@psionline.com).
